我叫巴里·艾伦
My name is Barry Allen,
是现今世上速度最快的人
and I am the fastest man alive.
在外人看来
To the outside world,
我只是个普通的鉴证专员
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist.
但在尖端科研实验室的朋友们的帮助下
But secretly, with the help of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
我秘密地打击犯罪  寻找跟我一样的超能力者
I fight crime and find other meta-humans like me.
但是我在时间中迷失了
But I became lost in time.
我的朋友们用尽了一切办法才把我救回来
It took everything in my friends' power
但我们的世界
to bring me back, and in doing so
也因此出现了新的威胁
our world was opened up to new threats.
我是唯一来得及阻止他们的人
And I'm the only one fast enough to stop them.
我是闪电侠
I am the Flash.
《闪电侠》前情回顾
Previously on "The Flash"...
你是这么看我的吗  某种邪恶秘书吗
Is that what you think I am? Some sort of evil secretary?
你说呢
You tell me.
我将永远是我丈夫的伙伴
I am now, and forever will be, my husband's partner.
幸会  多米尼克·兰斯
Pleased to meet you, Dominic Lance.
你好  艾伦先生
Hello, Mr. Allen.
迪沃  若你伤害我的家人
Devoe, if you hurt my family--
我对你的家人没有兴趣
I have no interest in your family.
而且等你消失后总得有人
Besides, you're gonna need someone
思念你
to miss you when you're gone.
-你做了什么  -我只是给你留了一样东西
- What did you do? - I left something for you.
我不再需要它了
I don't have need for it anymore.
巴里·艾伦  你因谋杀
Barry Allen, you're under arrest
克利福德·迪沃被捕了
for the murder of Clifford Devoe.
中城警局
我是一个无辜的人
And I'm an innocent man.
我知道你们会在他身上
I know that you'll find my fingerprints
提取到我的指纹
all over his body.
还会在我身上提取到他的DNA
And I know that you'll find his DNA on mine.
案发现场  请勿跨越
但我不知道谁捅了他
But I don't know who stabbed him...
也不知道他怎么会出现在我阁楼里
Or how he ended up in my loft.
我只能告诉你们我是被陷害的
All I can tell you is I'm being framed...
我什么也没有做
For something I didn't do.
我没有杀害克利福德·迪沃
I didn't kill Clifford Devoe.
好吧  艾伦
All right, Allen,
咱们从开头来回顾一遍
let's run it back from the beginning.
闪 电 侠
第四季
第十集
这就是迪沃想要的
This is exactly what Devoe wanted.
我们都按他的计划进行  尤其是我
I mean, we all played right into his plan, especially me.
迪沃为什么要安排这一切
Why would Devoe want to orchestrate all of this?
不知道  但我知道这一切开始于
I don't know, but we know that this started
我还困在神速力的时候
when I was still in the Speed Force.
但目标为什么是多米尼克
But why target Dominic?
多米尼克的超能力肯定允许迪沃
Dominic's power must have allowed Devoe
寄居在他的身体内
to inhabit his body.
我们该早些发现的
We should've been on top of this earlier.
那巴士上其他超能力者呢
What about the other metas on the bus?
为什么创造出他们
Why create them?
更大的计划中的一部分吗
Part of a larger plan?
你怎么现在在这里  艾伦
How are you even here right now, Allen?
你不是被捕了吗
Aren't you on house arrest?
-是这样  -他现在其实在乔那里
- Yeah, well-- - He's at Joe's, actually.
或者是在法庭
Either that or the courthouse.
我设法黑入了脚踝监视器的GPS
I managed to hack into the ankle monitor GPS.
这不是西斯科黑入的唯一一样东西
That's not the only thing Cisco hacked.
你从神速力出来的时候
When you came out of the Speed Force,
就在中城警局胡言乱语
you were talking gibberish at CCPD.
你说到不想杀谁
You said something about not wanting to kill anyone.
我当时抹去了这段视频
I digitally scrubbed a video.
我们最不想要的就是有人听到了
Last thing we want is somebody hearing something
我们不想让他们听到的东西
we don't want them to hear.
法官大人  我是无辜的  这不是我干的
Your Honor, I'm innocent. I didn't do this.
我没有杀人
I didn't kill anyone.
我不记得说过这些
Yeah, I mean, I don't remember saying any of that.
-不记得  -对
- You don't? - No.
我们得看看他刚从神速力出来后
We should look at everything else he said
说的其他所有东西
when he first came out of the Speed Force.
-也许会有线索  -好主意
- Might give us a clue. - That's a good idea.
大伙儿  记住
Okay, guys, but remember,
鉴于他们手上针对我的那些证据
I mean, considering all the evidence they have against me,
这次庭审甚至持续不了很久
this trial is not even gonna last very long.
好  但塞西尔休假
Okay, but with Cecile taking a leave of absence
为你辩护  你有了镇上最厉害的律师
to represent you, you got the best lawyer in town.
-好  -就算他们给你定罪
- Yeah, - I mean, even if they did find you guilty,
也没监狱能关住你
it's not like any prison can hold you.
我并不打算逃跑  我不想做逃犯
Well, I'm not gonna run. I won't be a fugitive.
如果我被宣告有罪  我得去监狱
If I'm convicted, I have to go to prison.
我们不会让这事发生的
We're not gonna let that happen.
好  我们回去工作吧
Right. Let's get to work.
得去法院了
We should get to the courthouse.
好
Yeah.
-你还好吗  -他们说第一年婚姻
- How you doing? - They say the first year
总是最难的
of marriage is always the hardest,
但我从未想过我丈夫面临谋杀罪的指控
but I never thought my husband being on trial for murder
会是挑战之一
would be one of the challenges.
我们一起经历了这么多
We have been through so much.
这次也会挺过去的
We'll get through this too.
对不对  巴里
Will we, Barry?
我知道神速力那段时间给了你对生活的新看法  但
I know the Speed Force gave you a new outlook on life, but...
我不知道现在保持积极是不是就够了
I don't know if being positive is enough right now.
我只是想为团队为了你坚强起来
I'm just trying to be strong for the team and for you.
记住  我们是闪电侠队
Remember, we're The Flash.
我们是闪电侠队
We're The Flash.
拉尔夫  等等
Ralph, hold up.
我不会让巴里入狱的
Listen, I'm not gonna let Barry go to prison.
我辜负了他的父亲  不能再辜负他
I failed his dad, I'm not gonna fail him.
我需要你的帮助
I need your help.
我的帮助  伸缩的那种帮助吗
My help, huh? As in the stretchy kind?
是卑鄙的私家侦探那种
As in the underhanded private investigator kind.
-我不见怪  -快来
- Oh, ha, no offense taken. - Come on.
科学技术研究了很久  需要什么要素
Science has long pondered what would be required
才能够成功地把一个生命体的意识传送到
to successfully transfer consciousness
另一个生命体中
from one living being to another.
但是我们做到的不仅仅是
But we've accomplished far beyond
简单地转移意识
a simple transfer of consciousness.
我们萃取了提升了人性的部分
We've extracted that which elevates our humanity
还给它添加了
and added upon it.
我既是从前的我
I am both who I was before...
也是我渴望成为的我
and who I desire to become.
是的  我的爱人
Yes, you are, my love.
我的手在你身上还是感到有些陌生
My hand still feels foreign upon your flesh.
你却并不介意
And you don't care for it.
是的
No, I do.
如我所说  我继承了宿主读心的能力
As I said, I inherited my host's ability to read thoughts.
我们从前不会对对方撒谎
We have never lied to each other before.
现在也不要这样
Let's not begin now.
好的
Okay.
马尔利泽  我的爱人
Marlize, my love...
透过这副躯壳
See past this body.
透过这双眼睛
See past these eyes.
看到我  克利福德
See me, Clifford.
没有你我什么也不是
I am nothing without you.
法官大人  陪审团的女士们先生们
Your Honor, ladies and gentleman of the jury,
中城法院
如果你们不明白今天我将要告诉你们的
If you don't understand what it is I'm about to tell you today,
你们得做个准备
you need to do something.
我需要你们相信不可能
I need you to believe in the impossible.
孩童时期  我们被教导
As children, we're taught that
警察是保护我们的  为我们服务的
the police are there to protect us, to serve.
我们被告知纳税是为了让他们
We're told that our tax dollars go toward training them
作为城市的守护者
to be the champions of the city.
但对于我们中的一些人而言  一个中城
But for some of us, it still seems impossible
最优秀的警局鉴证员竟会背叛我们的信任
that a police investigator, one of Central City's finest,
这种事依然难以置信
could betray that trust.
更可怕的是  他作为执法人员
And even worse, under the guise of upholding the law
居然犯下骇人听闻的罪行
to commit the most heinous act
做出一个人所能对别人做出的最恶劣行径
that one person can carry out against another.
但这就是巴里·艾伦的所作所为
But that is exactly what Barry Allen did.
现在  起诉将会证明  毫无疑问
Now, the prosecution will prove beyond any doubt
众人之中的他就是一头披着羊皮的狼
that he stood among us a wolf in sheep's clothing.
但事情是这样的
But here's the thing.
巴里·艾伦戴着面具
Barry Allen wears a mask,
利用他与法律的纽带
used his connection to the law,
以及作为鉴证科专员的职务经历
his experience as a police investigator,
尤其是作为犯罪现场技术人员的经验
especially as a crime scene technician,
跟踪受人尊敬的教授同时也是身为丈夫的
to stalk a beloved professor and husband
克利福德·迪沃  并冷血地谋杀了他
and murder Clifford Devoe in cold blood.
鲍温先生  在划线处签名
All right, Mr. Borwin, just sign on the dotted line
你的储蓄账户就设立好了
and your savings account is all set up.
谢谢  我想把这个弄对
Appreciate your helping me out, I want to get this right.
这是我第一个储蓄户头
It's my first savings account.
-你还好吗  -没事
- You okay? - Yeah.
大概只是午餐前有些头晕
Just a little lightheaded before lunch, I guess.
祝你一天开心
Have a great day.
禁令
女士们先生们  我手上的这份文件
Ladies and gentleman, the document in my hand,
是一份由法庭发布的禁令
it's a court-issued restraining order.
发给死者马尔利泽·迪沃的妻子
It's issued to Marlize DeVoe, the wife of the victim,
代表她的丈夫
on behalf of her husband
反对巴塞洛缪·亨利·艾伦先生
against a Mr. Bartholomew Henry Allen.
如果你们想看得清楚点  我这有更大的拷贝
Now if you'd like a better look, I have a bigger copy.
如果你们允许  我想念出来
And if you'll allow me to call out
写在下面的发布禁令的理由
what's written underneath "Reason for order issue,"
骚扰
harassment.
被告几天前被人发现
The defendant was seen just days earlier,
非法闯入死者家中
illegally breaking and entering into the victim's house,
到处翻查死者的物品
searching through the victim's effects.
纠缠不清
A man obsessed.
在死者的指甲里
Barry Allen's skin cells were found
找到了巴里·艾伦的皮肤纤维
under the nails of the victim.
如果可以的话  大家想像一下
Now imagine that, if you can,
迪沃先生  一个坐在轮椅上的人
Mr. DeVoe, a man in a wheelchair,
就在艾伦先生想要制服他时
desperately trying to defend himself
他拚命地想要保护自己
as Mr. Allen sought to overpower him.
最后  杀死克利福德·迪沃的
And finally, this is the knife
就是这把刀
that was used to kill Clifford DeVoe.
如果刀看起来崭新  是因为刀的确是新的
If it looks new, that's because it is.
这是艾伦先生收到的结婚礼物
It was a wedding gift to Mr. Allen.
现在我们来分析一下
Now let's just let that sink in for a moment.
这把刀本来是用来
This was supposed to commemorate
纪念一对情侣最开心的时刻
the most joyous moment in a couple's lives.
但是艾伦先生却用它来
But instead Mr. Allen used it
将一对情侣永远地分开
to forever separate a couple from one another.
他把结婚礼物用来做凶器
He used a wedding gift as a murder weapon.
那是一种特殊的罪恶
That is a special kind of evil.
被告对此完全漠视
Defendant showed an absolute disregard...
西斯科  市中心发生了超能力者袭击事件
Cisco, there's a meta attack downtown.
-我们得走了  -厚颜无耻  麻木不仁
- We got to go. - Brazen callousness...
我留下来陪巴里
I'll stay here with Barry.
这里结束之后
When you're done,
能去工作站帮帮我吗
could I get some coverage of the work stations?
警探  你能去录口供吗
Detective, would you get a statement please?
-拉蒙先生  -队长
- Mr. Ramon. - Captain.
-这里出了什么事  -古老的中城
- What happened here? - Well, vintage Central City.
又一起奇怪事件
aning another weird one.
没有数据外泄  没有物品被盗
No data breach, nothing stolen.
所有的人就这样倒下了
Everyone just collapsed.
我安排了警官去医院给他们录口供
I have officers at the hospital interviewing people now,
但是目前  没人知道情况
but so far, no one knows anything.
暗物质城
Dark matter city.
我们要对付的肯定是超能力者
Yeah, we're definitely dealing with a meta here.
你要不要看看这周围有什么要处理的吗
You want to see what kind of perimeter we're dealing with?
我正有此意
You read my mind.
乔  你确定能负责这件案子吗
Hey, Joe, you sure you're okay to run this case?
因为如果你需要多一点时间
Because I totally understand
我完全能理解
if you need a little more time, uh...
我没事  真的
Uh, I'm fine, really.
也许我晚点得去法庭
I may have to go over to the courthouse later.
我
Yeah, I'm, uh...
其实我也要去
I'm actually heading over there myself.
控方传召我出庭作证
The prosecution called me to testify.
对不起  乔
I'm sorry, Joe.
你知道我很关心巴里
You know how much I care about Barry,
但我必须据实以告
but I have to tell them what I know.
我明白  你必须做你该做的事
I get it, you got to do what you got to do.
是的
Yeah.
需要我重复一遍问题吗
Do I need to repeat the question?
不用  我听到了
No, I heard it.
站在克利福德·迪沃尸体旁边的是巴里·艾伦
The person standing over Clifford DeVoe's body was Barry Allen.
我没有问题了  法官阁下
No further questions, Your Honor.
辛格队长  你说五年前巴里·艾伦
Captain Singh, you stated that you interviewed
来应征犯罪现场鉴证员时  是你面试他的
Barry Allen five years ago for the job of CSI.
我想知道你当时对他的第一印象是什么
I wonder, what was your first impression of him?
他很年轻
He was young.
比起我面试的其他人  他只有一半经验
Had half the experience of everyone else I interviewed.
那你为什么请他
Why'd you hire him?
是因为他在面试中说的话
It was really something he said in the interview.
每个人总是说追查罪犯和犯人
Everyone always talks about going after the criminal, the guilty.
但艾伦却说他想帮助那些死者
But Allen said he wanted to help the victims.
帮助那些无辜的人
The innocents.
我认为中城应该有一个这样的人
I thought Central City deserved someone like that.
艾伦是好人中的一员
Allen is one of the good ones.
好人中的一员
One of the good ones.
我没有问题了  法官阁下
No further questions, Your Honor.
我想再次发问  法官阁下
I'd like to redirect, Your Honor.
请继续
Proceed.
如果有必要  你会为艾伦先生掩饰吗
Would you cover for Mr. Allen if you had to?
-当然不会  -不会
- No, of course not. - No.
他的个人档案上显示
It says here in his personnel file
他去捷克共和国休了六个月的假
that he took a six-month sabbatical to the Czech Republic.
他是先征得你的同意吗
Did he get approval from you first?
不完全是
Not exactly.
他说是因为私事
He said it was for something personal,
我相信他有充分的理由去
I'm sure he had a good reason to go.
拯救世界这个理由充分吗
Is saving the world a good reason?
档案上还显示  过去两年来
It also says in here that he was late
他迟到了72次
72 times in the past two years.
你有问过他理由吗
Did you ever ask him why?
没有  因为无论他什么时候到
No, because regardless of what time he got in,
他总是做好本职工作
he always did his job.
我只是好奇去想  他不去工作
I was just curious to imagine what he does
那他到底在干什么
with his time instead of being at work.
就像是他有秘密生活一样
It's almost like he has this secret life.
所以尽管他有这些违规行为
So in spite of all these infractions,
你从未想过处分他吗
you never thought to discipline him?
你想说什么
What are you suggesting?
想说不管你是否意识到
That whether you realized it or not,
几年来你一直在帮艾伦先生
you've been covering the ugly truth
掩饰这些丑恶的事实
about Mr. Allen for years now.
不是这样的
That is not true.
那他在攻击和骚扰迪沃先生是真的吗
Is it true that he was targeting and harassing Mr. DeVoe?
是还是不是
Yes or no?
是  所以我同意迪沃先生申请禁令
Yes, which is why I granted DeVoe the restraining order
叫艾伦保持距离
and told Allen to stay away.
但这却没能阻止他  不是吗
But that didn't stop him, did it?
他还是继续追击迪沃先生
He kept going after him right up until the night
-直至他遇害的那晚  -反对  纯属猜测
- that Mr. DeVoe was killed. - Objection! Conjecture.
收回
Withdrawn.
队长  你说过艾伦先生
Captain, now, you said that Mr. Allen
想要帮助受害者或是无辜的人
wants to help the victims, or the innocents.
但失踪几个月
But disappearing for months at a time
迟到72次
and being late 72 times
听起来除了他自己
doesn't sound like he wants to help
他并不想帮助  并不在乎任何人
or care for anybody but himself.
你现在还认为他是好人中的一员吗
Now, do you still think that he's one of the good ones?
希望你的看法是正确的
Hope you're right about this.
相信我
Oh, trust me,
我非常善于解读肢体语言
I'm very good at reading body language.
现在你很紧张
Right now, you're tense.
现在很生气
Huh, now you're annoyed.
有发现
Here we go.
-搞定  -拍到了吗
- Yahtzee. - Did you get that?
拉尔夫拍到了
Oh, Ralphie got it.
我觉得案子会宣判无罪
I smell an acquittal.
正如我们所想的那样  我们有麻烦了
As we thought might happen, we are in trouble.
大卫的证词给我们造成了不小的影响
David's testimony hurt us,
但我们还有几个选择
but we still have a few options.
什么选择
What are they?
我可以去找斯莱特  我可以申请认罪协议
I can go to Slater, I can ask for a plea deal,
也许能让你的刑期缩短一点
maybe get you a shorter sentence.
或是我们可以以精神错乱为辩护理由
Or we could use an insanity defense.
不  这两个选择
No, both those options
都在承认我有罪  但是我并没有罪
are admitting I'm guilty, and I'm not.
好吧  那唯一的办法
Fine, then the only other way out of this
只有你自己作证
is for you to testify.
塞西尔  抱歉  我不会这么做的
Cecile, I'm sorry, I won't do it.
所有的证据  每一条证据都不利于你
All of the evidence, every bit of it, it points to you.
如果你不愿意出庭作证  为自己辩护
If you're not willing to take that stand and defend yourself,
那这案子就打不赢了
then this is an impossible case.
我不会出庭作证的
I'm not taking a stand.
巴里  即使那样意味着能打赢这场官司
Barry, even if that means turning this case around
不用坐牢呢
and not going to jail?
爱瑞丝  如果我作证  我就必须撒谎
Iris, if I testify, I have to lie.
我就犯下作伪证罪  变成他们认为的那种人
I commit perjury, I become exactly who they think I am.
那就别撒谎
Then don't lie.
-什么  -告诉他们真相
- What? - Tell the truth.
告诉所有的人你是闪电侠
Tell everyone you're The Flash.
巴里  如果法庭知道你是闪电侠
Barry, if the court knows you're The Flash,
那你就可以解释所有的事  他们会相信你的
then you can explain everything and they'll believe you.
起诉很快就要结束了
Prosecution's gonna wrap up soon.
我今天就要得到你的回答
I need your answer today.
这是唯一的办法  巴里
This is the only way, Barry.
告诉这个城市你是闪电侠
Tell the city you're The Flash.
就这么点吗
This is all we got?
-这可没什么帮助  -我知道  好吗
- This isn't a lot to go on. - I know, okay?
我们能搞到这个录像就已经很幸运了
We're lucky we even got this footage.
-为什么  -不知为何
- Why? - For some reason,
所有监控摄像头都烧了
all the security cameras were fried.
各位  我刚去了医院
Hey, guys, I was just at the hospital
查看当时银行里
going over the medical records
所有人的医疗记录
of everyone who was at the bank.
我知道他们为什么晕倒了
I know why they passed out.
他们为什么晕倒了
Why did they pass out?
他们都出现了神经衰弱
Well, they all suffered from fatigue,
呕吐  腹痛  皮肤红疹
vomiting, abdominal pain, skin rashes.
所以所有人都吃了过期的卷饼吗
So everyone ate a bad burrito?
不  是辐射中毒
No, radiation poisoning.
这就是为什么所有摄像头都被烧了
That's why the security cameras are fried.
咱们得找出这家伙来
We got to find this guy
以免他把整个城市都毒了
before he poisons the whole city.
是啊  或是更糟的
Yeah, or worse.
各位  如果这个超能力者能让那些病人
Guys, if this meta can cause these levels of radiation
受到如此程度的辐射  那就意味着
in these patients, that means this meta
他的构成和核弹一样
has a similar makeup to a nuclear bomb.
所以是那种能把咱们炸上天的量吗
So, like, enough to blow us all up?
咱们谈的是什么样的严重程度
What are we talking here?
核爆产生的辐射
The fallout from a nuclear explosion
可能是毁灭性的
could be catastrophic.
-没错  -辐射
- Exactly. - Fallout.
-好名字  -可怕的能力
- Great name. - Terrible power.
好吧  我去看看卫星
Okay, I'll see if the satellite
能不能追踪他的能量信号
can track his radiation signature.
迪沃夫人  你何时第一次见的艾伦先生
Mrs. Devoe, when did you first meet Mr. Allen?
艾伦先生大概两个月前出现在我家
Mr. Allen showed up at my house almost two months ago
声称是在调查
claiming to be investigating
克利福德的一个前同事
one of Clifford's former colleagues.
我们告诉他我们没有能帮到他的信息
We reassured him that we didn't have information to help him.
但是艾伦先生持续不断的骚扰我先生
But Mr. Allen persisted and continued to harass my husband.
那是什么导致了限制令的呢
And what prompted the restraining order?
我的丈夫有
My husband has...
晚期肌萎缩侧索硬化症
had advancing ALS.
我大部分时间都和凯文单独在一起
I was alone with Kevin most of the time.
但是艾伦先生的激进态度
But something about Mr. Allen's aggressive manner
让我感到不安  于是我们就找了警察
just made me feel unsafe, so we went to the authorities.
我们以为投诉能够阻止艾伦先生
And we thought the complaint would dissuade Mr. Allen.
但是却没有
But it didn't.
你能向法庭描述下
Could you please describe for the court
最后一次见到丈夫时的情形吗
the last time that you saw your husband?
当时是圣诞节
It was Christmas.
克利福德想要和艾伦先生谈谈
And Clifford wanted to confront Mr. Allen.
他希望就着圣诞精神
He had hoped that in the holiday spirit,
他可以劝他远离我们
he could convince him to let us be.
但我...
And I--
我祈求克利福德不要去
I begged Clifford not to go.
但是即便有着残疾
But even with his disability,
克利福德依然坚持作为丈夫
Clifford insisted that it was his job
他有职责要保护我们  保护我
as my husband to protect us, to protect me.
他不想活在恐惧中  所以...
He didn't want to live in fear, so...
他走了...
He left...
我真想  我真希望我阻止了他
And I wish--I wish I could have stopped him
挡在他面前告诉他不要这么做
and stepped in and told him not to do this.
但是我让他离开了
But I let him go.
没有进一步的提问了  法官大人
No further questions, Your Honor.
法官大人  我想将物品F加入证据中
Your Honor, I would like to enter exhibit F into evidence.
反对  法官大人
Objection, Your Honor.
为什么这个没有加入发现名单之中
Why wasn't this entered into discovery?
我是最近才收到这个证据的
Oh, I've only recently received this new evidence.
我能继续了吗
May we approach?
法官大人  这里有违反协议
Your Honor, there are protocols that need to be observed.
这是我的法庭  斯莱特先生
This is my courtroom, Mr. Slater.
我会按照我的意愿来进行
I'll run it any way I see fit.
我允许
I'll allow it.
这些相片是今天早些时候拍摄的
These photographs were taken earlier today.
迪沃夫人
Mrs. Devoe.
你能告诉我们
Could you tell me please
这照片里和你接吻的男人是谁吗
who is the man that you're kissing in that photograph?
这显然不是你的丈夫  对吗
It is most certainly not your husband, correct?
他名叫多米尼克·兰瑟
His name is Dominic Lanse.
你认识兰瑟先生多久了
And how long have you known Mr. Lanse?
几个月
A few months.
那么在我看来也许你的婚姻
So it appears to me that perhaps your marriage
没有你描述的那么美满
was not quite as perfect as you've portrayed.
也许你想要一个没有你丈夫的生活
Maybe you were ready for a life without your husband.
所以你闯进了别的男人的怀里
So you ran into the arms of another man,
一个被你说服杀掉你丈夫的男人
another man you convinced to kill your husband.
克利福德和我是在几个月前的一个
Clifford and I met Dominic Lanse
硬化症慈善晚会上遇见的多米尼克·兰瑟
at an ALS charity gala months ago.
他是去纪念他父亲的
He was there to honor his father,
他在不久前因为这个病症去世了
who had recently passed away with the disease.
克利福德注意到了多米尼克和我的情感
Clifford noticed the bond that Dominic and I shared,
甚至是在我发觉之前
long before I did.
我的丈夫很高兴我找到了一个能交谈的人
My husband was happy that I found someone to talk to,
而他怂恿我去找多米尼克
and he urged me to turn to Dominic
来获取他所不能提供的满足和需求
for the needs and comforts he could no longer fulfill.
我的丈夫想让我幸福
My husband wanted me to be happy.
克利福德没有把我和多米尼克的关系
Clifford didn't see my relationship with Dominic
看成分离我们的工具
as a tool to pull us apart
反而是让我们更紧密
but to bring us together.
事实也确实如此
And it did.
我的心永远属于克利福德
My heart will always belong to Clifford.
没有进一步的问题了  法官大人
No further questions, Your Honor.
你可以离开了
You're excused.
这可不太顺  你做出决定了吗  巴里
Okay, that did not go well. What's your decision, Barry?
我不会做的
I'm not gonna do it.
马尔利泽
Marlize.
韦斯特·艾伦夫人  如果让别人看到
Mrs. West-Allen, I don't think it's appropriate
我们俩在交谈可不太好
for the two of us to be seen talking.
算了吧  没有人在看
Oh, please. No one is watching,
你可以不用再演荒唐戏了
so you can drop that ridiculous act already.
如果你坚持的话
If you insist.
你为什么要这样
Why are you doing this?
你是有什么问题
What is wrong with you?
这不是我有什么问题
It's not about what's wrong with me.
而是这世界出了什么问题
It's what's wrong with the world.
现在有比你丈夫更大的问题
There are problems bigger than your husband.
比如呢
Such as?
不管你想干什么
Whatever it is that you are up to,
都会迎来终结
it will come to an end.
真有激情  我之前也有
Such passion. I had that too
就在我和克利福德刚结婚的时候
when Clifford and I first got married.
但是激情会减淡  而剩下的
But passion fades, and what remains,
如果你幸运的能像克利福德和我一样
if you are fortunate enough like Clifford and I,
那就是比热情更深的东西  你无法摧毁
is something deeper than ardor that cannot be destroyed.
那你为什么那么坚决的要摧毁我们的生活
Then why are you so hell-bent on destroying our lives?
我只是尽全力帮助
I am doing what I have to do
我的丈夫而已  韦斯特·艾伦夫人
for my husband, Mrs. West-Allen.
你真正应该询问的问题
The question you should truly be asking
是你能为你的那位做到什么程度
is, what are you willing to do for yours?
希望你能喜欢接下来的戏
Hope you enjoy the rest of the show.
法院还没有消息
Still no word from the courthouse.
那是好消息  对吗  没消息就是好消息
That's good news, right? No news is good news?
不  好消息是好消息
No, good news is good news.
没有消息是传达错误
No news is miscommunication.
卫星在主街上发现了
The satellite was able to track a spike in radiation
-辐射量尖峰  -找到他了
- downtown on Main Street. - We found him.
辐射在逃跑
Fallout's on the move.
咱们得快点赶过去
We got to get down there now.
我在这里监视他
I'll monitor him from here.
-哈里  开始作战吧  -好
- Harry, time to book it. - Yep.
读数到了二
I got two rads.
停下
Hey, hey, stop!
停下  停下
Stop! Stop!
停下
Stop!
这里是怎么了
What's going on out there?
核废料处理小组
核废料运输车
Nuclear waste tanker.
抱歉
Sorry!
-混蛋  -好吧
- Idiots. - Okay.
走吧
Move along.
斯莱特先生  叫下一个证人吧
Mr. Slater, call your next witness.
谢谢  法官大人
Thank you, Your Honor.
法官大人
Your Honor.
现在你需要知道一些事
There's something you need to know right now
等下会影响这个案子的结果
that will alter the outcome of this case.
韦斯特·艾伦夫人  我不知道
Mrs. West-Allen, I have no idea
你是想干什么
what you think you're doing.
解释我丈夫为什么不肯
Explaining what my husband won't.
巴里·艾伦是
Barry Allen is...
闪
The Fla--
怎么回事
What's happening?
我们移动很快  其他人都相对静止了
We're moving so quickly that everyone else is still.
你怎么能带着我这么做
How are you able to do this with me?
我真不知道
I actually don't know.
爱瑞丝
Iris, hey.
我已经决定不告诉任何人我是谁
I already decided not to tell anyone else who I am.
巴里  如果陪审团知道你是闪电侠
Barry, if the jury knew that you were The Flash,
他们就不会判你有罪了
there is no way that they would convict you.
我要尽力保护你
I'm trying to protect you, okay?
如果每个人都知道我的秘密
If everyone knew my secret,
我们就得一直跑
we would never stop running.
我情愿和你一起一直跑
I would rather run forever with you
也不想没有你
than stand alone without you.
不仅仅是咱俩得不停跑
It wouldn't just be us running.
过去四年我们周边的每个人
Everyone that has stood by us the last four years
背后都有人追赶
would have a target on their back.
如果罪犯知道我的名字
If criminals knew my name,
他们就会知道我的弱点
they'd know my weakness.
我会尽力变得强大的  巴里
I'm trying to be strong, Barry.
我知道
I know.
我不能
I can't anymore.
你怎么能呢
How can you?
我父亲  他也经历过
My dad. He went through this too.
审判还没结束  巴里
The trial is not over, Barry.
没错
Yeah, it is.
所有的证据都指向我
All the evidence points towards me.
不能告诉他们  好吗
Can't tell them, okay?
好
Okay.
韦斯特艾伦夫人
Yes, Mrs. West-Allen?
法官大人
Your Honor...
巴里·艾伦
Barry Allen...
是无罪的
is innocent.
我觉得你们都应该知道这点
And I just thought you all should know that.
谢谢您
Thank you for your time. Okay.
如果有假慈悲奖
If there was an award for best crocodile tears
去授予最能操纵情感的寡妇
by the most emotionally manipulative widow,
马尔利泽肯定在前三
Marlize, definitely in the top three.
咱们得挖出比热吻更有爆料的信息
Let's snap something more damning than a lip lock.
我们来这可不是干那个的
We're not here for that.
你能发挥你恶心的伸展技能
Can you do your gross stretchy thing
伸到里面打开门吗
and slip inside and open the door?
那是地毯纤维
Those are carpet fibers.
是艾伦家的  对吗
Those are from Allen's loft, aren't they?
你要捏造证据栽赃马尔利泽
You're gonna plant evidence to frame Marlize.
她是唯一一个
She was the only one
能放置迪沃尸体的人
that could have planted Devoe's body.
她鞋底花纹上的纤维
Fibers on the treads of her shoes
证明她在犯罪现场
places her at the crime scene.
这是正确的  拉尔夫
This is the right thing to do, Ralph.
快打开门  我来做其他的
Just open the door. I'll do the rest.
好
Okay.
真是个可靠的计划啊  乔
It's a solid plan, Joe.
难以觉察  但很狡猾  还有点伤感
Subtle, but it's crafty with a touch of pathos.
这之后  你就没事啦  轻松了
After this, you're gonna sit back and kick up your feet
在火人节后舒舒服服睡上好一阵子
and sleep as sound as a millennial after Burning Man
因为你做了正确的事
because you did the right thing.
你干掉了一个坏女人
You took down a bad, bad chick.
拉尔夫  你能快点嘛
Ralph, could you hurry up?
然后你就享受这种感觉
And you're gonna ride that feeling
就像坐太空飞车一样
like it's Space Mountain.
然后当他们抓住你
And then when they catch you
拿走你的警徽和枪
and they take your badge and your gun,
那自以为是的愤慨
that self-righteous indignation
会使你昂首挺胸
is gonna keep your chest puffed and your chin up
因为你做了正确的事
because you did the right thing.
当然  你会生个几年气
Sure, you're gonna be mad for a few years,
但终会消气
but that fades.
会变化
It evolves,
转为自怜
turns into self-pity.
再过几年
A few more years, and...
你的生活就会变成原来的空壳子
your life is gonna be a shell of its former self.
然后  一天晚上
And then, one night,
你会渐渐明白
it's gonna dawn on you that
你做了错误的选择
you did the wrong thing.
会毁了一切
It's gonna ruin everything.
你的同事不再理你
Your colleagues won't talk to you,
你的朋友全都消失了
your friends have vanished.
至于你的家人
And your family?
就好像
It'll be like...
好像你从未出生
Like you were never born.
因为你变成了那种人
Because you turned into the very thing
那种你发誓要保护家人不受其伤害的人
that you swore to protect them from.
无论如何
Anywho...
祝你好运
Good luck with that.
斯莱特先生
Mr. Slater?
控方陈述完毕  法官大人
The prosecution rests, Your Honor.
霍尔顿女士  你准备好阐述了吗
Ms. Horton, are you ready to present your case?
辩方阐述完毕  法官大人
The defense rests, Your Honor.
应该坚持以精神失常为借口
Should've gone with the insanity plea.
对不起
Excuse me.
怎么了
What's wrong?
发生什么了
What is going on?
辐射出现骤增
There's a massive spike in radiation downtown,
在普伦蒂斯和罗林斯路交口
at Prentice and Rawlins.
核废料卡车的司机
The driver of the nuclear waste truck.
辐射指数已经达到3000还在攀升
Radiation signature's already at 3000 rads and climbing.
我们得在达到10000前阻止他
We need to stop this guy before it hits 10,000.
到达10000会怎样
What happens at 10,000 rads?
就像广岛那样
Hiroshima.
巴里·艾伦将其一生都
Barry Allen has dedicated his life
奉献给中城
in service of Central City.
他帮助我们破了无数的犯罪案件
He's helped us solve countless crimes.
他的证词帮助
His testimony has led to the conviction
给几十个罪犯定罪
of dozens of criminals.
巴里·艾伦是个好人
Barry Allen is a good man.
他是无罪的
He's an innocent man.
说实话  中城有他是幸运
And frankly, Central City is lucky to have him.
容我这么说
Dare I say...
这个城市里很少有人能这样
Few men in this city are as honest,
诚实  正直  可靠
upstanding, and dependable.
艾伦先生
Mr. Allen?
法官大人  我
Your Honor, I...
我得离开
I have to go.
巴里  你在干嘛
Barry, what are you doing?
我得走
I have to.
超能力者警报
对不起  法官大人  紧急事件
I'm sorry, Your Honor, this is an emergency.
有人需要我
Someone needs me.
我需要你尊重我的法庭
And I need you to respect my courtroom.
我不能容忍戏剧性的中断
I will not stand for theatrical disruptions.
法官大人  我的客户保释期间是自由的
Your Honor, uh, my client is still free on bail.
没有法律规定他
And there are no laws that require him
必须出席最后陈述
to be present during closing statements.
请注意  艾伦先生
Be advised, Mr. Allen.
法律规定
You are required by law
你得在这接受判决
to be here for sentencing.
明白  法官
Yes, Your Honor.
待在那别动
Stay where you are!
我这是怎么了
What is happening to me?
不许动  就在那
Hold it, right there!
我什么也没做
I didn't do anything!
-你得停下来  -我不想伤害任何人
- You need to stop. - I don't want to hurt anybody.
我明白  但你的放射性很危险
I understand, but your radioactivity is dangerous.
-各位  -7500
- Guys? - 7,500 rads!
巴里  别离他太近
Barry, don't get too close to him, all right?
他放射的辐射
The radiation he's emitting
太热了  你来不及自我修复
is too hot to allow you to self-heal.
嗯  谢谢提醒
Yeah, thanks for the heads-up.
我该怎么做  我怎么才能阻止他
What am I supposed to do? How do I stop him?
我停不下来
I can't stop this!
我们得冷却他
Oh, damn. We need to cool him down.
冰霜杀手
Killer Frost.
-太好了  -快  变身
- Great. - Well, go, turn!
可不是这么变的
Well, that's not how it works.
我不能打个响指就让她出现
I can't just snap my fingers and make her appear.
只有当我害怕和生气时才行
It only happens when I'm scared or angry.
天啊  凯特琳
Oh, good Lord, Caitlin.
这个城市都要爆炸了
The city's about to explode!
你所认识和所爱的所有人所有东西
Everyone, everything you know and love,
小鸟  树木  鱼
the birds, the trees, the fish,
小狗
the puppies!
小狗会死去
The puppies are going down
因为你不想
because you didn't want to...
变身工作
show up for work!
谢谢
Thanks.
-还不错是不是  -没错
- That was pretty good, yeah? - That was pretty good.
-赶快出发  -好的
- Now go already! - Okay!
好了  出发吧
Okay, there you go.
怎么回事
What's going on?
有任务了还是想我了
Is this business or a social call?
看来是有任务了
Business, I see.
-她还好吗  -她没事
- She okay? - She's gonna be okay, yeah.
还有别的办法吗
Do you have any more ideas?
我应该瞄准哪里
Where do I breach him?
拉蒙不行...
Ramon, no, you...
你会把他引爆
You drop him a breach, he could explode.
"辐射"的辐射会把我们都杀死
And Fallout's fallout would kill us all.
你觉得呢
Do you think?
如果我能让他周围形成真空呢
Wait, what if I create a vacuum around him?
那样就算他爆炸了
That way, even if he does explode,
我们也能控制住范围
at least we contain the blast.
没错  没错艾伦
Yeah, yes, Allen, yes.
办法可行  可以控制住范围
That--that could work, that could contain it.
不管怎么做  要尽快
Whatever you're gonna do, though, do it fast.
辐射已经超过八千拉德了
Fallout just went above 8,000 rads.
真空控制住了他的能量
The vacuum's containing his energy.
很好
Good.
但他的能量还在增长
But he's still getting stronger.
艾伦  我不知道你还能承受多久这种辐射
Allen, I don't know long you can take this much radiation.
我别无选择
I don't have a choice.
我们必须要控制住他
We have to contain his energy.
艾伦  九千拉德了
Allen, 9,000 rads.
一万拉德  已经到临界值了
10,000 rads, critical mass.
拉蒙  你得把能量引开
Ramon, you need to send that energy somewhere.
什么  引去哪里
What? To where?
地球十五  地球十五是一颗死星
Earth-15, Earth-15 is a dead Earth.
快打开缺口
Breach it there now!
你做到了  天啊你做到了
You did it. Oh, man, you did it.
你拯救了世界
You saved the day.
陪审团的女士们先生们
Ladies and gentleman of the jury,
你们是否已经有了结论
you've reached a verdict?
是的  法官大人
We have, Your Honor.
全体起立
All rise.
针对案卷5567-B
For Docket Number 5567-B,
对于巴塞洛缪·亨利·艾伦的起诉
in the matter of The People vs. Bartholomew Henry Allen,
陪审团判定为
we, the jury, find the defendant
一级谋杀罪
guilty of murder in the first degree.
幸亏你有超常的代谢能力
Thanks to your meta metabolism,
你体内的辐射
your radiation burns should disappear
很快就会消失了
in the next few minutes.
-辐射怎么样了  -他很不稳定
- What about Fallout? - He's unstable,
我们会把他送到特蕾西的实验室
but we sent him to Tracy's lab.
她会分析他的DNA
She's gonna analyze his DNA,
看有没有和他一样的超能力者
see if it's the same as the other best metas
就能把他的能力中和掉了
and then we'll be able to neutralize him.
几分钟前  在最高法院
Superior Court, where minutes ago,
陪审团判定巴塞洛缪·亨利·艾伦
the jury found Bartholomew Henry Allen
谋杀克利福德·迪沃教授罪名成立
guilty in the murder of Professor Clifford Devoe.
过去五年里
Mr. Allen has been a CSI
艾伦先生在中城警局
with the Central City Police Department
从事犯罪现场调查工作
for the last five years.
不久后
In just a few short hours,
法官就会宣布对艾伦先生的判决
the judge is expected to announce Mr. Allen's sentence.
诉讼官安东·斯莱特表示
Prosecutor Anton Slater made a statement.
鉴于犯罪情节的恶劣
He hoped Mr. Allen would receive a life sentence,
他希望艾伦先生被判终身监禁...
given the brutal nature of the cri...
我本想亲口告诉你
I wanted to be the one to tell you.
这一切简直难以置信
I can't believe this is happening.
别这样  我们刚刚拯救了世界
Come on, guys, we just saved the city today.
我们早就知道结果会不尽人意
We knew this wasn't gonna go my way in court.
这不代表我们被迪沃打败了
That doesn't mean that Devoe beat us.
无论如何  我们都会继续战斗
Whatever happens, we're gonna keep fighting.
是的
I know.
你得回去了
We need to get you back.
宣判的时候你要在场
You need to be there for sentencing.
没错
Yeah.
一会儿见
I'll see you guys later, all right?
我没事的
I'm gonna be okay, all right?
走吧
Come on.
你父亲的事
You know you got your strength
让你有了坚强的力量
from watching your dad be your rock?
而你就是我的力量
I got mine because you're mine.
我会为了你坚强起来
I'll be strong for you.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
走吧
Come on.
-艾伦  -退后
- Allen... - Step back.
我一会儿就来
Yeah, I need a minute, all right?
艾伦夫人  你想过会这样吗
Mrs. Allen, did you expect this?
艾伦先生
Mr. Allen.
迪沃
Devoe.
你知道你有百分之十二的概率
Did you know there was a 12% chance
告诉大家你是闪电侠吗
that you were gonna tell the world you're The Flash?
你得重新算算了
I'd recheck your math.
没必要
There's no need.
因为无论你如何选择
Because no matter what path you chose,
结果都是一样的
all avenues led to my triumph.
你为什么要针对我们
Why do you want us distracted?
为什么一定要除掉我
Why do you want me out of the picture?
你在谋划什么
What are you planning?
你是永远无法理解
At you think that you could understand
我要做的事的
the breadth of what I'm about to do is almost humorous.
没错  你会想念爱瑞丝的
Yes, I think you will miss Iris.
没错艾伦先生
That's right, Mr. Allen.
我不只占据了多米尼克的身体
I didn't just take Dominic's body.
还拥有了他的能力
I took his ability.
我知道你此时此刻的想法
I know what you're thinking right now.
还是我亲口来说比较好
Well, I want you to hear me say it.
我一定会摆脱这件事
I'm gonna figure a way out of this.
那时候
And when I do,
无论你用着谁的面孔
I don't care who's face you're wearing.
我都不会放过你
I'm coming for you.
你还没有赢
You haven't beaten us yet.
没有吗
Haven't I?
生活愉快  艾伦先生
Have a nice life, Mr. Allen.
法官大人  我是无辜的
Your Honor, I'm innocent.
我没有做过那些事  我没有杀人
I didn't do this, I didn't kill anyone.
我相信  总有一天会真相大白
And I know that one day, the truth will come out.
谢谢
Thank you.
宣判请起立
Rise for sentencing.
我在这里工作了三十年
In my 30 years behind this bench,
曾见过许多罪犯
I have seen my share of criminals.
但这位被告与众不同
But I confess this defendant stands apart.
感谢各位来参加这次发布会
Thank you all for coming on such short notice.
几小时前  我们的城市
A few hours ago, the very existence of our city
面临着核武器爆炸的威胁
came under the threat of nuclear destruction.
但有一个人挺身而出
But one man rose to meet that challenge.
被告人身居要职
The defendant was in a position of authority.
我们相信他会将罪犯绳之以法
Our city trusted him to bring the guilty to justice.
尽管辐射会毁坏他的身体
He ran into danger,
他依然奋勇当先
knowing he would suffer burns all over his body.
他利用这份信任夺去了一条无辜而脆弱的性命
He used that trust to take an innocent and vulnerable life.
他不是为了自己
This man was not thinking about himself.
而是为了其他人
He was thinking about you.
他奋战在前线
The first responders on the front lines.
我从未见过如此冷漠之人
Never have I seen a defendant more unmoved.
我从未见过如此勇敢之人
Never have I seen a man with more bravery.
从未见过如此残忍之事
Never have I seen such inhumanity.
如此无畏之事
Such heroism.
如此漠视生命
Such a lack of regard for human life.
很荣幸向大家宣布
It is my great honor to present
中城警局最英勇奖
Central City Police Department's Award of Valor
献给这座城市的英雄
to this city's finest hero.
现今世上速度最快的人  闪电侠
The fastest man alive, The Flash!
现在法院判决巴塞洛缪·亨利·艾伦
The court hereby orders that Bartholomew Henry Allen
终身监禁
should be incarcerated for the rest of his natural life,
不得假释
without the possibility of parole
并立即将艾伦先生
and that Mr. Allen be immediately remanded
送押至铁山监狱
to Iron Heights Penitentiary.
愿上帝怜悯你的灵魂
And may God have mercy on your soul.
回头见  巴
Be seeing you around, B!
好好适应
Get comfortable.
亨利·艾伦曾
住于此